Review Exercise 11-7, Compound Nouns and Complex Verbs. 1. The wily old lighthouse
keepers invent a highly lucrative money laundering scheme once a season.
2. The wily old lighthouse keepers invented a highly lucrative money
laundering scheme last year.
3. The wily old lighthouse keepers are inventing a highly lucrative money
laundering scheme again.
4. The wily old lighthouse keepers will invent a highly lucrative money laundering
scheme if they aren't afraid of being caught and sent to prison.
5. The wily old lighthouse keepers will invent a highly lucrative money laundering
scheme if they weren't afraid of being caught and sent to prison.
Six, the wily old lighthouse keepers that have invented a highly lucrative money
laundering scheme if they hadn't been afraid of being caught and sent to prison.
Seven, the wily old lighthouse keepers that have invented a highly lucrative
money laundering scheme are languishing in club fed at the moment.
8. The wily old lighthouse keepers have invented a highly lucrative money
laundering scheme for the tenth year in a row.
9. The wily old lighthouse keepers had invented a highly lucrative money
laundering scheme long before multi-level marketing became popular.
10. The wily old lighthouse keepers will have invented a highly lucrative money
laundering scheme by the time they get back from checking their offshore bank
accounts.
11. The wily old lighthouse keepers ought to invent a highly lucrative money
laundering scheme to handle the overflow cash from their many nefarious
enterprises.
12. The wily old lighthouse keeper should invent a highly lucrative money laundering
scheme to stash their ill-gotten gains.
13. The wily old lighthouse keeper shouldn't invent a highly lucrative money
laundering scheme in this anti-crime climate.
14. The wily old lighthouse keepers should have invented a highly lucrative money
laundering scheme while they were in the witness protection plan.
15. The wily old lighthouse keepers shouldn't have invented a highly lucrative
money laundering scheme while they were being monitored by the FBI.
16. The wily old lighthouse keepers could invent a highly lucrative money laundering
run out of ideas.
17. The wily old lighthouse keepers couldn't invent a highly lucrative money
laundering scheme even if their lives depended on it.
18. The wily old lighthouse keepers could have invented a highly lucrative money
laundering scheme if they had a laptop and a bank account.
19. 20. Even those wily old lighthouse keepers couldn't have invented such a
highly lucrative money laundering scheme without outside help.
20. The wily old lighthouse keepers might invent a highly lucrative money laundering
scheme unless they're kept under house arrest.
21. The wily old lighthouse keepers might have invented a highly lucrative money
laundering scheme while they were waiting for trial.
22. The wily old lighthouse keepers must invent a lot of highly lucrative money
laundering schemes.
23. The wily old lighthouse keepers must have invented a highly lucrative money
laundering
24. The wildly old lighthouse keepers can invent hundreds of highly lucrative money
laundering schemes.
25. The wildly old lighthouse keepers can't invent any more highly lucrative
money laundering schemes.